OLEG OBIUKH

Kyiv • 099-531-3954 • oleg.obiukh@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/oleg-obiukh-237362139/ O olegobiukh.github.io/portfolio2019/

Front-end developer

Cumman	
Summar	y

I'm a result and a process-oriented person with strong theoretical background and good practical experience in Web development. Thorough and precise in everything I do, have a keen interest in technology, mobile applications and user experience.

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- LESS
- BEM
- Bootstrap 3/4
- Gulp
- Photoshop
- Figma

- JS (ES5, ES6)
- jQuery
- React/Redux
- Angular.js
- Git
- npm
- Jira

Portfolio:

https://olegobiukh.github.io/portfolio2019/

https://olegobiukh.github.io/fe6/

https://olegobiukh.github.io/FE/5/

https://olegobiukh.github.io/FE/1/

https://olegobiukh.github.io/react-sw/

Work experience

May.2019 - current day Front-end developer

Flepron

- Work with Angular.js, Bootstrap 3/4, jQuery
- Work on a large project
- English daily with team members
- Working with a team

Dec.2018 - Apr.2019 Front-end Developer

Freelance and Training projects

• Stack: JS, React

01.2018 - 10.2018 WordPress Developer

Web Idea Us

- WordPress. Added content to WordPress websites
- SEO. inner (WP) and outer
- Worked with Google Analytics and AdWords

Education

Design, Manufacture and Maintenance of Radio Equipment

College of Computer Technology and Economics